jahantv.com 2014-02-08

# Privacy Policy JahanTV

JahanTV.com is committed to protecting your privacy on-line. Because of Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), if your age is 13 or under, You can't use this website. If you do not want any cookies created from this website or third parties like Google, please don't use this website. For more information click HERE  
We use the information we collect about you to provide services to you when you visit the Site. We appreciate that you do not want any personal information you provide to us distributed indiscriminately and here, we explain how we collect information, what we do with it and what controls you have.

It is your responsibility to read and understand this Privacy Policy. If you do not understand or accept this Privacy Policy then you should contact us at [ info@jahantv.com](mailto:info@jahantv.com). If you do not agree to all of this Privacy Policy and do not wish to be bound by it, you are not authorised to access or otherwise use the Site.

**1\. Limitation Of Liability**

The Site may contain links to other websites where information practices may be different to ours. For example, if you "click" on a link, the "click" may take you off the Site. You should consult the other websites' privacy notices as we are not responsible for and have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

We may sometimes offer content (e.g., competitions or promotions) sponsored by or co-branded with identified third parties.  We are not responsible for and have no control over these third parties' use of this information. However, we will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if these third parties will obtain such information.

We may use a reputable third party to present or serve the advertisements that you may see at the Site. This Privacy Policy does not cover any use of information that a third-party ad server may have collected from you.

**2\. Legal Disclaimer**

We are not responsible nor will be liable to you in any way for events beyond our direct control. Because of the complex and constantly changing nature of our technology and business, we cannot guarantee nor do we represent that our performance will be error free, and to the maximum extent permitted by law we will not be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, consequential or punitive damages or other loss suffered by you and relating to the use. 

**3\. Updates**

We reserve the right, from time to time, and at our sole discretion, to change or update this Privacy Policy.

All changes to this Privacy Policy will be published on this page and on the Site. Upon publication, each change will become effective and you will be deemed to be aware of and bound by it. You should therefore review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure that you are up-to-date with the current terms of the Privacy Policy.

**4\. Cookies and Web Beacons**

www.jahantv.com does not use cookies. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your hard drive to store and sometimes track information about you. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can change your browser to prevent that. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of a website if you do so. Cookies are specific to the server that created them and cannot be accessed by other servers, which means they cannot be used to track your movements around the web. Although they do identify a user's computer, cookies do not personally identify users and passwords and credit card information are not stored in cookies.

DoubleClick DART Cookie 

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.jahantv.com. .:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.jahantv.com and other sites on the Internet. .:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following [URL](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). Alternatively, you can opt out of some third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting [aboutads](http://www.aboutads.info/).

We have not [opted out of third-party ad serving](https://support.google.com/dfp_sb/answer/94152?hl=en), the cookies of other [third-party vendors or ad networks](https://support.google.com/dfp_sb/answer/94149) may also be used to serve ads on our site, and should be disclosed in your privacy policy as well in the following manner.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....

Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.jahantv.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

www.jahantv.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.jahantv.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

The [DoubleClick cookie](https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/answer.py?answer=2839090) is used by Google in the ads served on the websites of its partners, such as websites displaying AdSense ads or participating in Google certified ad networks. When users visit a partner's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser.

Our privacy policy includes the following information:

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on user's prior visits to our website.

Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and/or other sites on the Internet

Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings.](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/) (Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info.).](http://www.aboutads.info/)

**4\. 3rd Party Cookies**

We have not [opted out of third-party ad serving,](https://www.google.com/support/dfp_sb/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=94152) the cookies of other [third-party vendors or ad networks](https://www.google.com/support/dfp_sb/bin/answer.py?answer=94149) may also be used to serve ads on our site, and is disclosed in our privacy policy as followed:

We notify our site visitors of the third-party vendors and ad networks serving ads on our site.

We provide links to the appropriate vendor and ad network websites by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/)

We inform our users that they may visit those websites to opt out of the use of cookies for interest-based advertising (if the vendor or ad network offers this capability). Alternatively, we direct users to opt out of some third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info.](http://www.aboutads.info/)

5\. Log Files

Like many other Web sites, www.jahantv.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

This Privacy Policy was last updated on Nov 4, 2013.
